{
    "Maths": [
        {
            "question_number": 1,
            "question": "If the first term of an A.P. is 3 and the sum of its first four terms is equal to one-fifth of the sum of the next four terms, then the sum of the first 20 terms is equal to",
            "options": [
                "-1080",
                "-1020",
                "-1200",
                "-120"
            ],
            "answer": "-1080"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 2,
            "question": "One die has two faces marked 1, two faces marked 2, one face marked 3 and one face marked 4. Another die has one face marked 1, two faces marked 2, two faces marked 3 and one face marked 4. The probability of getting the sum of numbers to be 4 or 5, when both the dice are thrown together, is",
            "options": [
                "(1)",
                "(2)",
                "(3)",
                "(4)"
            ],
            "answer": "(2)"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 3,
            "question": "Let the position vectors of the vertices A, B and C of a tetrahedron ABCD be i + 2j + k, i + 3j – 2k and 2i + j - k respectively. The altitude from the vertex D to the opposite face ABC meets the median line segment through A of the triangle ABC at the point E. If the length of AD is √10 and the volume of the tetrahedron is √805/6√2, then the position vector of E is",
            "options": [
                "(7i+j+3k)",
                "(i+4j+7k)",
                "(12i+12j+k)",
                "(7i+12j+k)"
            ],
            "answer": "(7i+12j+k)"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 4,
            "question": "If A, B, and (adj (A¯¹) + adj (B-1)) are non-singular matrices of same order, then the inverse of A(adj (A-1) + adj (B-1))¯¹ B, is equal to",
            "options": [
                "AB-1 + A1 B",
                "adj (B-1) + adj (A-1)",
                "AB + BA",
                "AB (adj(B) + adj(A))"
            ],
            "answer": "AB (adj(B) + adj(A))"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 5,
            "question": "Marks obtained by all the students of class 12 are presented in a frequency distribution with classes of equal width. Let the median of this grouped data be 14 with median class interval 12-18 and median class frequency 12. If the number of students whose marks are less than 12 is 18, then the total number of students is",
            "options": [
                "52",
                "48",
                "44",
                "40"
            ],
            "answer": "44"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 6,
            "question": "Let a curve y = f(x) pass through the points (0,5) and (loge 2, k). If the curve satisfies the differential equation 2(3 + y)e^{2x}dx - (7 + e^{2x})dy = 0, then k is equal to",
            "options": [
                "4",
                "32",
                "8",
                "16"
            ],
            "answer": "8"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 7,
            "question": "If the function f(x) = {sin (k1 + 1)x + sin (k2 - 1)x},x < 0; 4, x = 0; 2+k1x^2+k2x loge(x), x > 0 is continuous at x = 0, then k1 + k2 is equal to",
            "options": [
                "20",
                "5",
                "8",
                "10"
            ],
            "answer": "10"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 8,
            "question": "If the line 3x – 2y + 12 = 0 intersects the parabola 4y = 3x² at the points A and B, then at the vertex of the parabola, the line segment AB subtends an angle equal to",
            "options": [
                "tan^{-1}(...)",
                "tan^{-1}(...)",
                "tan^{-1}(...)",
                "-tan^{-1}(...)"
            ],
            "answer": "tan^{-1}(...) (2)"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 9,
            "question": "Let P be the foot of the perpendicular from the point Q(10, -3, -1) on the line ... Then the area of the right angled triangle PQR, where R is the point (3, -2, 1), is",
            "options": [
                "9√15",
                "√30",
                "8√15",
                "3√30"
            ],
            "answer": "3√30"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 10,
            "question": "Let the arc AC of a circle subtend a right angle at the centre O. If the point B on the arc AC, divides the arc AC such that ..., and OC = αOA + βOB, then α + √2(√3 – 1)β is equal to",
            "options": [
                "2√3",
                "2 - √3",
                "5√3",
                "2 + √3"
            ],
            "answer": "2 - √3"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 11,
            "question": "Let f(x) = loge x and g(x) = ... Then the domain of fog is",
            "options": [
                "[0,∞)",
                "[1,∞)",
                "(0,∞)",
                "R"
            ],
            "answer": "R"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 12,
            "question": "If the system of equations λx + (λ – 1)y + (λ – 4)z = 5; (λ – 1)x + (λ + 1)y – (λ + 2)z = 9; (λ + 1)x + (λ + 2)y – (λ + 2)z = 9 has infinitely many solutions, then λ² + λ is equal to",
            "options": [
                "6",
                "10",
                "20",
                "12"
            ],
            "answer": "12"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 13,
            "question": "The number of words, which can be formed using all the letters of the word \"DAUGHTER\", so that all the vowels never come together, is",
            "options": [
                "36000",
                "37000",
                "34000",
                "35000"
            ],
            "answer": "36000"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 14,
            "question": "Let R = {(1, 2), (2, 3), (3, 3)} be a relation defined on the set {1, 2, 3, 4}. Then the minimum number of elements, needed to be added in R so that R becomes an equivalence relation, is:",
            "options": [
                "10",
                "7",
                "8",
                "9"
            ],
            "answer": "7"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 15,
            "question": "Let the area of a △PQR with vertices P(5, 4), Q(−2, 4) and R(a, b) be 35 square units. If its orthocenter and centroid are O (2, ...) and C(c, d) respectively, then c + 2d is equal to",
            "options": [
                "...",
                "...",
                "...",
                "3"
            ],
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 16,
            "question": "The value of ∫ dx is",
            "options": [
                "2",
                "loge 2",
                "1",
                "e^2"
            ],
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 17,
            "question": "Let ... , z ∈ C, be the equation of a circle with center at C. If the area of the triangle, whose vertices are at the points (0,0), C and (a, 0) is 11 square units, then a² equals:",
            "options": [
                "50",
                "100",
                "...",
                "..."
            ],
            "answer": "100"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 18,
            "question": "The value of (sin 70°) (cot 10° cot 70° - 1) is",
            "options": [
                "2/3",
                "1",
                "...",
                "3/2"
            ],
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 19,
            "question": "Let I(x) = ∫ dx. If I (37) -I(24) = ... + (b+c), b, c ∈ N, then 3( b + c) is equal to",
            "options": [
                "22",
                "39",
                "40",
                "26"
            ],
            "answer": "39"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 20,
            "question": "If ... ≤ x ≤ ..., then cos^{-1} (cos x + sinx) is equal to",
            "options": [
                "x-tan^{-1}...",
                "x + tan^{-1}...",
                "x-tan^{-1}...",
                "x + tan^{-1}..."
            ],
            "answer": "x-tan^{-1}... (3)"
        }
    ],
    "Physics": [
        {
            "question_number": 26,
            "question": "A point particle of charge Q is located at P along the axis of an electric dipole 1 at a distance r as shown in the figure. The point P is also on the equatorial plane of a second electric dipole 2 at a distance r. The dipoles are made of opposite charge q separated by a distance 2a. For the charge particle at P not to experience any net force, which of the following correctly describes the situation",
            "options": [
                "~ 10",
                "~ 20",
                "~ 0.5",
                "~ 3"
            ],
            "answer": "~ 3"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 27,
            "question": "A spherical surface of radius of curvature R, separates air from glass (refractive index = 1.5 ). The centre of curvature is in the glass medium. A point object ' O ' placed in air on the optic axis of the surface, so that its real image is formed at ' I ' inside glass. The line OI intersects the spherical surface at P and PO = PI. The distance PO equals to",
            "options": [
                "5 R",
                "3 R",
                "1.5 R",
                "2 R"
            ],
            "answer": "5 R"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 28,
            "question": "The position of a particle moving on x-axis is given by x(t) = A sin t + B cos² t + Ct² + D, where t is time. The dimension of ... is",
            "options": [
                "L²T⁻²",
                "L²",
                "L",
                "L³T"
            ],
            "answer": "L²T⁻²"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 29,
            "question": "Given a thin convex lens (refractive index μ₂), kept in a liquid (refractive index μ₁, μ₁ < μ₂) having radii of curvatures |R₁| and |R₂|. Its second surface is silver polished. Where should an object be placed on the optic axis so that a real and inverted image is formed at the same place?",
            "options": [
                "(1)",
                "(2)",
                "(3)",
                "(4)"
            ],
            "answer": "(1)"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 30,
            "question": "Refer to the circuit diagram given in the figure. Which of the following observations are correct? A. Total resistance of circuit is 6Ω B. Current in Ammeter is 1A C. Potential across AB is 4 Volts. D. Potential across CD is 4 Volts E. Total resistance of the circuit is 8Ω. Choose the correct answer from the options given below:",
            "options": [
                "A, B and D Only",
                "A, B and C Only",
                "A, C and D Only",
                "B, C and E Only"
            ],
            "answer": "A, B and D Only"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 31,
            "question": "Given below are two statements: Statement I: The hot water flows faster than cold water Statement II: Soap water has higher surface tension as compared to fresh water. In the light above statements, choose the correct answer from the options given below",
            "options": [
                "Statement I is true but Statement II is false",
                "Statement I is false but Statement II is true",
                "Both Statement I and Statement II are false",
                "Both Statement I and Statement II are true"
            ],
            "answer": "Statement I is true but Statement II is false"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 32,
            "question": "Consider a circular disc of radius 20 cm with centre located at the origin. A circular hole of radius 5 cm is cut from this disc in such a way that the edge of the hole touches the edge of the disc. The distance of centre of mass of residual or remaining disc from the origin will be",
            "options": [
                "2.0 cm",
                "1.5 cm",
                "1.0 cm",
                "0.5 cm"
            ],
            "answer": "1.0 cm"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 33,
            "question": "The electric flux is φ = ασ + βλ where A and σ are linear and surface charge density, respectively. ... represents",
            "options": [
                "electric field",
                "area",
                "charge",
                "displacement"
            ],
            "answer": "displacement"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 34,
            "question": "A sub-atomic particle of mass 10^{-30} kg is moving with a velocity 2.21 × 10^6 m/s. Under the matter wave consideration, the particle will behave closely like (h = 6.63 × 10^{-34} J.s)",
            "options": [
                "Visible radiation",
                "Gamma rays",
                "Infra-red radiation",
                "X-rays"
            ],
            "answer": "X-rays"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 35,
            "question": "Consider a moving coil galvanometer (MCG): A. The torsional constant in moving coil galvanometer has dimensions [ML² T⁻²] B. Increasing the current sensitivity may not necessarily increase the voltage sensitivity. C. If we increase number of turns (N) to its double (2N), then the voltage sensitivity doubles. D. MCG can be converted into an ammeter by introducing a shunt resistance of large value in parallel with galvanometer. E. Current sensitivity of MCG depends inversely on number of turns of coil. Choose the correct answer from the options given below:",
            "options": [
                "A, D Only",
                "A, B, E Only",
                "B, D, E Only",
                "A, B Only"
            ],
            "answer": "A, D Only"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 36,
            "question": "LIST-I: A. Pressure varies inversely with volume of an ideal gas. B. Heat absorbed goes partly to increase internal energy and partly to do work. C. Heat is neither absorbed nor released by a system. D. No work is done on or by a gas. LIST-II: I. Adiabatic process II. Isochoric process III. Isothermal process IV. Isobaric process. Choose the correct answer from the options given below:",
            "options": [
                "A-III, B-IV, C-I, D-II",
                "A-I, B-IV, C-II, D-III",
                "A-III, B-I, C-IV, D-II",
                "A-I, B-III, C-II, D-I"
            ],
            "answer": "A-III, B-IV, C-I, D-II"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 37,
            "question": "The electric field of an electromagnetic wave in free space is E = 57 cos [7.5 × 10⁸ t - 5 × 10⁻³(3x + 4y)] (4i – 3j) N/C. The associated magnetic field in Tesla is",
            "options": [
                "B = cos [7.5 × 10⁸ t - 5 × 10⁻³(3x + 4y)] (k)",
                "B = - cos [7.5 × 10⁸ t - 5 × 10⁻³(3x+4y)] (k)",
                "B = -- cos [7.5 × 10⁸ t - 5 × 10⁻³(3x + 4y)] (5/2)",
                "B = cos [7.5 × 10⁸ t - 5 × 10³(3x + 4y)] (5k)"
            ],
            "answer": "B = cos [7.5 × 10⁸ t - 5 × 10⁻³(3x + 4y)] (k)"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 38,
            "question": "A gun fires a lead bullet of temperature 300 K into a wooden block. The bullet having melting temperature of 600 K penetrates into the block and melts down. If the total heat required for the process is 625 J, then the mass of the bullet is grams. (Latent heat of fusion of lead = 2.5 × 10⁴ J/kg and specific heat capacity of lead = 125 J/kg K)",
            "options": [
                "10",
                "20",
                "5",
                "15"
            ],
            "answer": "5"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 39,
            "question": "What is the lateral shift of a ray refracted through a parallel-sided glass slab of thickness 'h' in terms of the angle of incidence 'i' and angle of refraction 'r', if the glass slab is placed in air medium?",
            "options": [
                "h tan(i-r)",
                "h sin(i-r)",
                "h",
                "h cos(i-r)"
            ],
            "answer": "h tan(i-r)"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 40,
            "question": "A radioactive nucleus n₂ has 3 times the decay constant as compared to the decay constant of another radioactive nucleus n₁. If initial number of both nuclei are the same, what is the ratio of number of nuclei of n₂ to the number of nuclei of n₁, after one half-life of n₁?",
            "options": [
                "1/8",
                "8",
                "4",
                "1/4"
            ],
            "answer": "1/8"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 41,
            "question": "A light hollow cube of side length 10 cm and mass 10 g, is floating in water. It is pushed down and released to execute simple harmonic oscillations. The time period of oscillations is yπ × 10⁻² s, where the value of y is (Acceleration due to gravity, g = 10 m/s², density of water = 10³ kg/m³)",
            "options": [
                "6",
                "2",
                "4",
                "1"
            ],
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 42,
            "question": "Regarding self-inductance: A. The self-inductance of the coil depends on its geometry. B. Self-inductance does not depend on the permeability of the medium. C. Self-induced e.m.f. opposes any change in the current in a circuit. D. Self-inductance is electromagnetic analogue of mass in mechanics. E. Work needs to be done against self-induced e.m.f. in establishing the current. Choose the correct answer from the options given below:",
            "options": [
                "A, B, C, E only",
                "B, C, D, E only",
                "A, C, D, E only",
                "A, B, C, D only"
            ],
            "answer": "A, C, D, E only"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 43,
            "question": "The motion of an airplane is represented by velocity-time graph as shown below. The distance covered by airplane in the first 30.5 second is km.",
            "options": [
                "12",
                "3",
                "6",
                "9"
            ],
            "answer": "9"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 44,
            "question": "Identify the valid statements relevant to the given circuit at the instant when the key is closed. A. There will be no current through resistor R. B. There will be maximum current in the connecting wires. C. Potential difference between the capacitor plates A and B is minimum. D. Charge on the capacitor plates is minimum. Choose the correct answer from the options given below:",
            "options": [
                "A, C Only",
                "A, B, D Only",
                "C, D Only",
                "B, C, D Only"
            ],
            "answer": "C, D Only"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 45,
            "question": "A solid sphere of mass 'm' and radius 'r' is allowed to roll without slipping from the highest point of an inclined plane of length 'L' and makes an angle 30° with the horizontal. The speed of the particle at the bottom of the plane is v₁. If the angle of inclination is increased to 45° while keeping L constant. Then the new speed of the sphere at the bottom of the plane is v₂. The ratio v₁ : v₂ is",
            "options": [
                "1:√2",
                "1:√√3",
                "1:3",
                "1:2"
            ],
            "answer": "1:√2"
        }
    ],
    "Chemistry": [
        {
            "question_number": 51,
            "question": "Given below are two statements: Statement I: Fructose does not contain an aldehydic group but still reduces Tollen's reagent Statement II: In the presence of base, fructose undergoes rearrangement to give glucose. In the light of the above statements, choose the correct answer from the options given below.",
            "options": [
                "Both Statement I and Statement II are true",
                "Both Statement I and Statement II are false",
                "Statement I is true but Statement II is false",
                "Statement I is true but Statement II is false"
            ],
            "answer": "Both Statement I and Statement II are true"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 52,
            "question": "The complex that shows Facial - Meridional isomerism is:",
            "options": [
                "[Co(en)2Cl2]+",
                "[Co(en)3]3+",
                "[Co(NH3)3Cl3]",
                "[Co(NH3)4Cl2]+"
            ],
            "answer": "[Co(NH3)3Cl3]"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 53,
            "question": "FeO2- FeO2 Fe3+ Fe2+ Feº In the above diagram, the standard electrode potentials are given in volts (over the arrow). The value of E is",
            "options": [
                "2.1 V",
                "1.7 V",
                "1.4 V",
                "1.2 V"
            ],
            "answer": "1.4 V"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 54,
            "question": "The element that does not belong to the same period of the remaining elements (modern periodic table) is:",
            "options": [
                "Iridium",
                "Platinum",
                "Osmium",
                "Palladium"
            ],
            "answer": "Palladium"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 55,
            "question": "Match the LIST-I with LIST-II: A. Molecules obeying octet rule B. Molecules with incomplete octet C. Molecules with incomplete octet with odd electron D. Molecules with expanded octet",
            "options": [
                "A-IV, B-I, C-III, D-II",
                "A-IV, B-II, C-I, D-III",
                "A-II, B-IV, C-III, D-I",
                "A-III, B-II, C-I, D-IV"
            ],
            "answer": "A-IV, B-II, C-I, D-III"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 56,
            "question": "What amount of bromine will be required to convert 2 g of phenol into 2,4,6-tribromophenol? (Given molar mass in gmol¯¹ of C, H, O, Br are 12, 1, 16, 80 respectively)",
            "options": [
                "20.44 g",
                "4.0 g",
                "6.0 g",
                "10.22"
            ],
            "answer": "6.0 g"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 57,
            "question": "Which among the following react with Hinsberg's reagent?",
            "options": [
                "A, B and E Only",
                "A, C and E Only",
                "C and D Only",
                "B and D Only"
            ],
            "answer": "A, C and E Only"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 58,
            "question": "The correct set of ions (aqueous solution) with same colour from the following is:",
            "options": [
                "Sc³+, Ti³+, Cr+",
                "V²+, Cr³+, Mn³+",
                "Ti⁴+, V⁴+, Mn²+",
                "Zn²+, V³+, Fe³+"
            ],
            "answer": "V²+, Cr³+, Mn³+"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 59,
            "question": "Given below are two statements: Statement I: In Lassaigne's test, the covalent organic molecules are transformed into ionic compounds. Statement II: The sodium fusion extract of an organic compound having N and S gives prussian blue colour with FeSO₄ and Na₄[Fe(CN)₆] In the light of the above statements, choose the correct answer from the options given below.",
            "options": [
                "Statement I is true but Statement II is false",
                "Both Statement I and Statement II are false",
                "Both Statement I and Statement II are true",
                "Statement I is false but Statement II is true"
            ],
            "answer": "Both Statement I and Statement II are true"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 60,
            "question": "Propane molecule on chlorination under photochemical condition gives two di-chloro products, \"x\" and \"y\". Amongst \"x\" and \"y\", \"x\" is an optically active molecule. How many tri-chloro products (consider only structural isomers) will be obtained from \"x\" when it is further treated with chlorine under the photochemical condition?",
            "options": [
                "2",
                "5",
                "4",
                "3"
            ],
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 61,
            "question": "CrCl₃·xNH₃ can exist as a complex. 0.1 molal aqueous solution of this complex shows a depression in freezing point of 0.558°C. Assuming 100% ionisation of this complex and coordination number of Cr is 6, the complex will be (Given Kf = 1.86 K kg mol¯¹)",
            "options": [
                "[Cr(NH3)5Cl]Cl2",
                "[Cr(NH3)6]Cl3",
                "[Cr(NH3)3Cl3]",
                "[Cr(NH3)4Cl2]Cl"
            ],
            "answer": "[Cr(NH3)4Cl2]Cl"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 62,
            "question": "Which of the following happens when NH4OH is added gradually to the solution containing 1 M A2+ and 1 M B3+ ions? Given : Ksp [A(OH)2] = 9 × 10⁻¹⁰ and Ksp [B(OH)3] = 27 × 10⁻¹⁸ at 298 K .",
            "options": [
                "Both A(OH)2 and B(OH)3 do not show precipitation with NH4OH",
                "A(OH)2 will precipitate before B(OH)3",
                "B(OH)3 will precipitate before A(OH)2",
                "A(OH)2 and B(OH)3 will precipitate together"
            ],
            "answer": "A(OH)2 will precipitate before B(OH)3"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 63,
            "question": "The major product of the following reaction is: CH3CH2CH = O excess HCHO, alkali, reflux",
            "options": [
                "...",
                "CH3-CH2-CH2-OH",
                "CH3-C-CH=O",
                "CH3-CH-CH=O"
            ],
            "answer": "CH3-CH2-CH2-OH"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 64,
            "question": "Ice at -5°C is heated to become vapor with temperature of 110°C at atmospheric pressure. The entropy change associated with this process can be obtained from",
            "options": [
                "Cp m dT + ΔHfusion, ΔHvaporisation...",
                "Cp m dT + ΔHfusion ΔHvaporisation...",
                "Cp dT+rev...",
                "Cp dT+..."
            ],
            "answer": "Cp m dT + ΔHfusion, ΔHvaporisation..."
        },
        {
            "question_number": 65,
            "question": "The incorrect statement among the following is",
            "options": [
                "PH3 shows lower proton affinity than NH3.",
                "SO2 can act as an oxidizing agent, but not as a reducing agent.",
                "PF3 exists but NF5 does not.",
                "NO2 can dimerise easily."
            ],
            "answer": "SO2 can act as an oxidizing agent, but not as a reducing agent."
        },
        {
            "question_number": 66,
            "question": "2.8 × 10⁻³ mol of CO2 is left after removing 10²¹ molecules from its 'x' mg sample. The mass of CO2 taken initially is Given: Na = 6.02 × 10²³ mol⁻¹",
            "options": [
                "98.3 mg",
                "48.2 mg",
                "196.2 mg",
                "150.4 mg"
            ],
            "answer": "98.3 mg"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 67,
            "question": "Match the LIST-I with LIST-II: Name reaction/Product obtainable: A. Swarts reaction B. Sandmeyer's reaction C. Wurtz Fittig reaction D. Finkelstein reaction",
            "options": [
                "A-II, B-I, C-III, D-IV",
                "A-II, B-III, C-I, D-IV",
                "A-IV, B-I, C-III, D-II",
                "A-IV, B-III, C-I, D-II"
            ],
            "answer": "A-II, B-III, C-I, D-IV"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 68,
            "question": "Heat treatment of muscular pain involves radiation of wavelength of about 900 nm. Which spectral line of H atom is suitable for this? Given : Rydberg constant RH = 10⁵ cm¯¹, h = 6.6 × 10⁻³⁴ J s, c = 3 × 10⁸ m/s)",
            "options": [
                "Balmer series, ∞ → 2",
                "Lyman series, ∞ → 1",
                "Paschen series, ∞ → 3",
                "Paschen series, 5 → 3"
            ],
            "answer": "Paschen series, ∞ → 3"
        },
        {
            "question_number": 69,
            "question": "The d- electronic configuration of an octahedral Co(II) complex having magnetic moment of 3.95 BM is:",
            "options": [
                "t2g³eg",
                "t2g⁶eg¹",
                "t2g⁵eg²",
                "eg²t2g³"
            ],
            "answer": "t2g⁵eg²"
        }
    ]
}